== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Leonard:)This is cool.
(Leonard:)When was the last time you
and I built something together?
(Howard:)Scientifically?
A little over a year ago.
(Howard:)LEGOs? Last week in my room.
(Leonard:)If there was a Nobel prize
for Millennium Falcons
(Leonard:)that fall apart when
you pick them up, we'd be set.
Hey, guys!
BOTH: Hey.
(Leonard:)What are you doing here?
(Bernadette:)We heard there were
some sexy scientists
(Bernadette:)working hard all weekend.
Yeah,
(Penny:)so we brought you some lunch and
we are gonna go look for 'em.
(Leonard:)Soup, sandwiches
and emasculation,
(Leonard:)just like my mom
used to make.
(Penny:)So, how's it goin'?
(Leonard:)Good. Slow.
(Howard:)There's a lot of tedious setup,
but once we get through that
(Howard:)it should go quicker.
(Penny:)Is there anything
we can do to help?
(Leonard:)You know what,
this part isn't that technical.
(Leonard:)You actually could.
(Penny:)Wow, really? Called my bluff.
All righty then.
(Bernadette:)Can we really help?
(Howard:)While we finish soldering
these boards, it'd be great
(Howard:)if you guys could wrap these
pipe fittings with Teflon tape.
(Leonard:)I'll show you
how to do one.
Hey, w-wouldn't it be funny
(Penny:)if after all your years
of hard work,
(Penny:)I'm the one who makes
a scientific breakthrough?